Hello. Thank you for the happy
birthday greeting. I just got done
with dinner here at Aunt Pat's
and my cousin Tricia came over and
her husband Don and we had a really
chill dinner. It was
very nice and had an amazing soup
before the dinner and amazing
dessert and amazing ice
cream. Anyway, now I feel really
super full and it's like nine
o'clock so I'm just gonna chill
and watch some either alien or
ghost YouTube channels that I like.
There's a couple guys
from England that I think you would
like them. They go into old busted
up buildings and they
find weird shit. Anyway, I'll stop
rambling on. The reason I sent you
a video is because I want
to congratulate you on the driver's
test. The question I have for you
is this the written one
or is this getting in the car and
having somebody sit next to you
with the clipboard and telling
you to take a left and park here
and do this. So I just wonder what
test you passed. Regardless,
I'm happy that you passed your test
because it's one more thing done,
like done, and if it is the
road test I'm super excited for you
because then you know you you you
aren't stuck on campus. You
can jump in the car and go to
Ventura. You could go to GameStop
in Ventura or go to the mall or go
to the beach or whatever. Yeah you
don't have to sit around. I'm
stoked. Okay I'll wrap it up just
under two minutes. That's because
you and you and Dara dumped me at
my coach talks. Okay I'll leave
it there. I hope you're well. I
miss you guys a lot and yeah I'll
keep you posted. I may be starting
a new medical treatment for my
depression in the next couple weeks
and it could be it could be
potentially life-changing for me.
Like I won't have to break well
yeah I mean I won't have I
don't know if I will have
depression anymore. I guess the
results are different for different
people. Some people depression goes
away and never comes back. Other
people like comes back and they
need a little like they have a nose
spray that people use it's like
allergy when you have allergy
and spray up your nose. Anyway
leave it there. Three minutes now.
Okay have a good night. All of you
buddy thanks for sending me the
note. Until Aidan I say hello. I
text him all the time and I think
about him a lot and just curious
what he's up to. Oh and let me know
who you're pulling for in the
playoffs. NBA playoffs. I think
you're a clip-joint guy but hey
dude I'm like 20 minutes from
Denver.
It's way closer than Ohio to LA.
I'm way closer to Denver. Be super
cool to get playoff tickets
and go see the Joker. Okay. Bye.